



# Gökay Özsoy

**Date of birth:** 02/03/1999 | **Nationality:** Turkish | **Phone number:** 

(+49) 15754860837 (Mobile) | **Email address:** gokayozsoy0@gmail.com | **Website:** 

https://gkyzsy.github.io/ Address: Borsteler Chaussee 72, 22453, Hamburg, Germany (Home)

#### ABOUT ME

## Computer Engineer / Junior Software - Web Developer

I am a computer engineer with experience in various areas. I love developing creative software and maintaining code & databases. My main programming language is JavaScript at the moment. I have recently developed a 2d action-packed web game using vanilla JavaScript, HTML5 Canvas, CSS, and Sprite animations. **Feel free to check it on my portfolio link!** 

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

17/09/2017 - 03/07/2023 Ankara, Türkiye

**COMPUTER ENGINEERING TED University** 

Website <a href="https://www.tedu.edu.tr/en">https://www.tedu.edu.tr/en</a> | Field of study Information and Communication Technologies | Level in EQF EQF level 6 |

National classification 6 | Type of credits ECTS | Number of credits 246

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

25/08/2024 - 21/09/2024 Berlin, Germany

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN KREATIVSTORM**

- Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC)
- WRSPM Model
- Methodologies (Waterfall, Agile, Kanban, etc.)
- Microservices
- API

Email <a href="mailto:contact@kreativstorm.de">contact@kreativstorm.de</a> | Website <a href="mailto:https://www.kreativstorm.de/">https://www.kreativstorm.de/</a>

08/08/2022 - 11/08/2023 Ankara, Türkiye

### JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ZKR NURSE CALL SYSTEMS

- Developed web forms and maintained and customized database for customers to observe user data. Maintained both front-end and back-end sides of projects by taking account of customer feedback.
- Arranged regular meetings with customers around the world. Planned the scope of Integration projects.
- Provided IT support through video calls and remote connection software (AnyDesk, TeamViewer).
- Developed a system management application on Linux to improve the production line's performance and to make basic daily operations easier.

Business or Sector Information and communication | Address Umit Mahallesi, Okullar Sokak, No.16, 6810, Ankara, Türkiye |

Email info@zkr.com.tr | Website https://www.zkr.com.tr/

22/06/2022 - 25/07/2022 Ankara, Türkiye

# **SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN** ZKR NURSE CALL SYSTEMS

- Learned frequently used technologies, tools, and programming languages in the company such as Qt Creator, PHP, JavaScript, C++, MySQL, etc.
- Handled the configurations of the company's products.

# DIGITAL SKILLS

Web

JavaScript | JSON | CSS | PHP | Linux | SQL | Angular | NestJS | MySQL | HTML5 canvas | HTML

**Back-End / Embedded / Desktop** 

Qt | C++ | Java

Network

TCP-IP | VoIP Systems

**Version Control / Methodologies** 

Github | Git | DevOPS (basic level)

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **TURKISH** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
GERMAN	B1	B1	B1	B1	В1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user